legendsofamerica.com 2018-01-29

# Privacy Policy – Legends of America

**The cliff notes of our Privacy Policy:**

We don’t use your information for spam, nor for anything nefarious. If you ever receive spam from us, please [let us know](https://www.legendsofamerica.com/about-us/#Contact) immediately. Your web browser settings have more control than we do. We don’t sell any information collected. We use [Google Adsense and Google Double Click for Publishers](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) for most of our advertising. These services have their own privacy policies. We use [GetResponse](https://www.getresponse.com/legal/privacy.html), a reputable, established company, as our Newsletter provider. This privacy policy pretty much covers everything, but we still have a separate [policy notice on our General Store](https://store.legendsofamerica.com/index.php?l=page_view&p=privacy_policy), as that is where we would collect more than just an email address and name. Our Photo Print Shop is hosted by Zenfolio.com which specializes in showcasing and sales of Photo Prints and other Products. [Zenfolio.com has it’s own privacy policy](https://en.zenfolio.com/privacy).

The rest of this is the legal mumbo jumbo that’s required for us to show you. If you read this entire message, you probably need to find a hobby…just sayin.

**Privacy Policy in full:**

Your privacy is very important to us. At Legends of America we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (Primarily we would ask for your name and email address when signing up for our newsletter. We also require email for making comments on our website.)

We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our website, or protect our rights.

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

Legends of America operates several websites including Store.LegendsOfAmerica.com, LegendsofAmerica.com, Photos.LegendsofAmerica.com, and LegendsOfKansas.com. It is Legends of America’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. [Legends’ General Store has it’s own privacy policy](https://store.legendsofamerica.com/index.php?l=page_view&p=privacy_policy) due to the fact we gather more information there when you place an order.  Legends’ Photo Print shop is hosted by [Zenfolio.com, which has its own privacy policy](https://en.zenfolio.com/privacy).

_Website Visitors_

Like most website operators, Legends of America collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Legends of America’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Legends of America’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Legends of America may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Legends of America also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our stories. Legends of America only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that website commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the website where the comment was left.

_Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information_

Certain visitors to Legends of America’s websites choose to interact with Legends of America in ways that require Legends of America to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Legends of America gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our website to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive Legends of America updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, Legends of America collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Legends of America. Legends of America does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.  
Aggregated Statistics

Legends of America may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Legends of America may monitor the most popular pages on the list25.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. Legends of America may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Legends of America does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

_Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information_

Legends of America discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Legends of America’s behalf or to provide services available at Legends of America’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Legends of America’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Legends of America will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Legends of America discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Legends of America believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Legends of America, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Legends of America website and have supplied your email address, Legends of America may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Legends of America and our products. We primarily use our various product websites to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Legends of America takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

_Cookies_

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Legends of America uses cookies to help Legends of America identify and track visitors, their usage of Legends of America website, and their website access preferences. Legends of America visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Legends of America’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Legends of America’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

_Business Transfers_

If Legends of America, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Legends of America goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Legends of America may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

_Ads_

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Legends of America and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. We use [Google Adsense and Google Double Click for Publishers](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) for most of our advertising.

_Comments_

Comments and other content submitted to Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

_Privacy Policy Changes_

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Legends of America may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Legends of America’s sole discretion. Legends of America encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
